《越狱》  前情回顾
Previously on Prison Break.
我把 信寄给你
When I sent you the envelopes
可不是闹着玩的
I wasn't just playing games.
靠近4号目标
Move on subject 4
执行命令
Execute the order.
求你不要这样做
Please don't do that.
你想要参与到这次行动中  现在机会来了
You wanted to get in on the action, here's your chance.
7.5亿美元的已经汇到卢森堡的一个帐户上了
3/4 of a billion dollars in a numerical account in Luxembourg.
所有数据将会在24小时内传输完毕
All the data will be delivered within 24 hours.
箱子给我
Case.
我来拿
I'll take that.
老妈  你好啊
Hi, mom.
我知道锡拉在你手上  把锡拉给我
I know you have it. Bring me scylla.
否则这次莎拉就真得死了
Or this time sara's death will not be faked.
看来你要做出抉择了
Looks like you have a little decision to make.
锡拉  还是你爱的人
Scylla -- or someone you Love.
好好考虑考虑  迈克
Just think this through, michael.
我考虑过了  两个人我们都要救
I have, and we're saving them both.
你怎么救?
How?
我会想出来的
I'll figure it out.
你哥哥快要失血过多而死了
Your brother is bleeding to death.
我想知道能不能把林肯和莎拉集中到一个地方
I wonder if we can bring lincoln and sara to the same place.
现在你唯一的优势就是两方都不知道
Right now your only advantage is that neither party knows
还有另一方手握你的人质
That there's another player that has leverage on you.
如果你把两人了集中到一起
You bring them both together
你就失去了战术优势
You'll lose your tactical edge.
我不会丢下莎拉的
I am not abandoning sara
我没让你那么做
I didn't say to do that
我的意思是...
What I am say is...
莎拉有没有中弹这个优势
sara has the advantage of not having a bullet in her chest.
一个一个来
One at a time.
令人吃惊
Big surprise.
蠢的那个被捉住了  聪明的那个逃跑了
The dumb one got caught, the smart one got away.
我都能总结出规律了
I'm beginning to see a pattern here.
他不会给你的
He's never going to give it to you.
我不这么认为  他真的很关心你
I disagree. He truly cares for you.
虽然事实证明你并不值得
No matter how many times you've shown you don't deserve it.
你们两个真是
You know, you two are truly
先天和后天因素影响的经典案例
A classic study nature versus nurture.
同样的环境  同样的父母
Same environment, same parents
你们却完全不同
You're completely different.
你觉得是为什么呢  林肯
Why do you think that is, lincolnoln?
因为他们的妈妈是个疯婆子
Because mom's a psychotic bitch.
你好啊  迈克
Hello, michael.
好吧  你赢了  我把锡拉给你
All right, you win. I'll give you scylla.
林肯需要什么就给他什么
Just give lincoln whatever he needs.
我还没得到我需要的东西呢
Not until I get what I need.
爱迪生装箱区B码头
Edison shipping yard, B dock,
45分钟内到达 带上我哥哥
45 minutes.and bring my brother
45分钟?  近一点
45 minutes? Cutting it close.
他看起来可不太妙
He doesn't look so good.
到那儿就是了
Just be there.
你觉得值吗  莎拉
Is it worth it, sara?
你有没有回想过那个晚上
You ever go back to that night
想过如果你当时
And wonder how things would have gone
锁了医务室的门  事情会变成怎样
If you had just left that infirmary door locked?
那些人的本来可以活下来的
All the people whose lives would have been saved.
你爸爸也是
Hell, your father would still be alive.
你有没有想到过这一点
You ever think about that?
现在既然迈克要把锡拉还给我了
And now that michael's returning scylla to me
你们这一切就白忙活了
It was all for nothing.
如果他真还给你了
Assuming he does return it.
如果情况相反  如果是迈克被抓了
If the situation were reversed, if michaelwere here
你手上有锡拉
And you were holding scylla,
你会怎么做
What would you do?
你会把锡拉带来的
You'd bring it back
和你没锁门是一个原因
For the same reason you left that door unlocked.
因为你不能眼睁睁看着无辜的人死掉
Because you couldn't let an innocent man die.
你的情感左右了你的理性判断
Your heart betrays your better judgment.
斯科菲尔德也是这样
So does scofield's.
你猜的没错
You know, you're probably right.
因为迈克从你鼻子底下把锡拉拿走的那天晚上
Because if michaelused his better judgment the night he
他如果理性判断的话
Stoll scylla out from under your nose
就会把你杀了
He would have killed you.
不要让我看见她
Get her out of my sight.
牵着
Take it.
要么你牵着我的口袋  要么我就牵你的
Either take my pocket or I take yours.
明白么
Understand?
当局正在街上进行地毯式搜查
The authorities are blanketing the streets
以搜寻主要嫌疑人
Looking for the primary suspects
林肯·布伦斯和迈克斯科菲尔德
lincoln·Burrows and michaelscofield.
因近几年来发生的
The brothers famous for
最胆大妄为的越狱行为而出名的
One of the most daring prison breaks in recent history
这对兄弟携有枪支并且极度危险
Are considered armed and extremely dangerous.
自制炸弹
Homemade explosives?
你有更好的主意吗
You got a better idea?
也许救你哥  救所有人  最好的方法是
Maybe the best way to save lincoln, to save everyone
给克里斯蒂娜她所想要的东西
Is to give christina what she wants.
我只是想找出一个保证我们挚爱的人
I am just trying to find a way where the people that we love
的安全的方法
don't end up in a autopsy table.
我不会让这件事发生的
And I am not.
你没弄错吧  阿历克斯
Better get your story straight, Alex.
你一直在说服我
This whole time you've been saying
把锡拉还给将军
You should give scylla back to the general.
你没听见他对赛尔夫的妻子做了什么吗
Didn't you hear what he did to self's wife?
赛尔夫自己自作自受
self made his own bed.
对  我们要收拾他的烂摊子
Yeah, we're sleeping with in it.
让我们想想  最好的结局
Let's say best case scenario.
我们也许能找到林肯和莎拉
Maybe somehow we're able to get to lincoln and sara.
然后呢
Okay. What then?
将军还派人监视着我的妻子
General've still got somebody watching my wife.
要怎么样保证她的安全?
What's the plan to keep her safe?
L.J呢?  又要怎么样保证他的安全?
What about L.J? What's the plan to keep him safe?
我现在考虑不到那么多
I can't thingk about that right now.
也许我们应该找你妈谈个条件
Maybe we go to your mother and try to make a deal.
她和将军是死对头了
I mean, there's no love lost with her and the general.
如果我们给她锡拉
With her contracts, if we give her scylla
有她的关系网络也许她能找到...
Maybe she can find out where the agents...
我们不会要调查  我们不会把锡拉还回去的
We're not finding out and not giving it back.
我们会救出所有人
We're going to save everyone.
你怎么会在这儿
What the hell are you doing here?
我怎么会在这儿
What am I doing here?
你在这儿康复  赛尔夫先生
You're in recovery, Mr. self.
看来你摔得不轻
Apparently you had quite a fall.
幸运的是有人发现了你并且报了警
Luckily someone found you and called 9-1-1.
他们做什么了
They did what?
医生马上就到  来查看你的历史记录
The doctor will be in shortly to go over your history.
不要  不要
No, no.
叫医生去给下一个人看病
Tell the doctor to go see the next guy.
我就走了
I'm going.
事实上  我不能让你走
Actually, I can't.
有人等着要和你谈话
There's men here waiting to talk to you.
什么样的人
What kind of men?
戴徽章的那种人
The kind with badges.
赛尔夫先生  我是克里斯·弗兰克探员
Mr. self, my name is Agent Chris Franco.
我们是FBI的
We're with the bureau.
我们想问你一些问题
We'd like to ask you a few questions.
什么问题
About what?
告诉我林肯·布伦斯
Start with where we can find lincoln·Burrows
和迈克斯科菲尔德在哪里
And michaelscofield.
准备好接我们
Be ready to pick us up.
爆炸的时候最好别离它太近
Better not get too close to that thing when it goes off.
你最好别走远
You'd better not get too far.
好吧
All right.
如果迈克有任何举动  就把他两个膝盖都打碎
If michaeltries anything, take out both knees.
我可不想让他死
I don't want him dead
只想让他动不了向我求饶
I just want him immobilized and eager to talk.
布伦斯怎么处理
And what do you want to do with burrows?
锡拉一到手  就把他丢到海里去
Once I get scylla, dump him off the dock.
喂  新闻里说的人
Yeah, one of the guys from the news.
我想我刚刚看见其中一个
I think i just seen him.
有趣的选择
Interesting choice.
我以为你会选择人多的地方
I would have thought you'd picked something a little more
好保护自己
Public for your own protection.
公共场所现在不利于我的安全
Something a little more public isn't safe for me right now.
拜你所赐
Thanks to you.
你一个人来的吗
Did you come alone?
你呢
Did you?
拜托
Come on.
我们至少能有一次不互相欺骗  对不对
We can have at least one honest conversation, can't we?
事实上  我想诚实
Actually, I'd like that.
不管你是怎么想的
In spite of what you think
我从未想要让你受伤
I never wanted to see you get hurt.
你想要什么
What did you want?
理解  原谅
Understanding, forgiveness.
我做出了自己的选择
I made my choice
我早知道我不会得到那些了
I knew I'd never have any of those things.
但你会拥有权利  不是吗
But you'll have power, won't you?
对  而你会拥有林肯
Yes, and you'll have lincolnoln.
老实说我觉得你非常不值
Honestly you're getting the short end of the stick.
说到林肯
Speaking of which
我要把他送去医院  他在哪儿
I need to get him to a hospital so where is he?
锡拉在哪儿
Where's scylla?
我要确信他还活着
I need to know he's alive.
满意了吧
Satisfied?
跟我来
Follow me.
现在  你不会耍什么鬼把戏的
Now, you wouldn't have some little trick up your sleeve,
是不是  儿子
Would you, son?
我不想再和你玩了
I'm done playing games with you.
很好
Good.
那把锡拉拿出来给我看
Then bring scylla out to me.
如果我把锡拉拿出来  你的手下就会射杀我
If I bring scylla out in the open, your man will shoot me.
那我们平手了
Then I guess we have a standoff.
唯一的区别是
The only thing is
我要的东西不是奄奄一息流血将尽的
what I want isn't gasping for air and losing a pinned of blood
把它给我  迈克
Give it to me, michael.
不行
I can't do that.
把它给我  迈克
Give it to me, michael.
你没有别的选择了
You're running out of options.
我说不行
I said, no.
我们是迈阿密警方
This is Miami Police.
把它给我  迈克
Give it to me, michael.
我们必须撤了
We got to go.
给我去拿
Go get it.
快走  迈克
Come on, michael.
迈克我们必须要走了
michael, we got to go now!
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
字幕：YYeTs人人影视字幕组  后期：zwzy_1007(胖胖)
《越狱》第四季 第二十一集
Prison.Break.S04E21
政府帮了你一把
So the government helped you out?
一起经历了这么多
After all we've been through
你知道那听起来有多疯狂吧
You know how crazy that sounds, Huh?
证据在那儿
Well, the proof is there.
每天早上我去叫醒宝贝女儿
Every morning when I wake up my little girl.
她现在又健康了
And she's healthy again.
你住在哪儿
Where are you living?
这就是我为什么来找你
Actually, that's why I came here to talk to you.
我们当时受监控  我等着
We were in productive custody, while I was waiting to
给马宏做不利证言  但后来案子不了了之
Testify against mahonebut the case fell through.
他们想要背信食言  还要把我
They wanted only renege on my deal but wanted to put my
重新关进福克斯河监狱
Ass back in fox river.
那你来芝加哥跟踪我干什么
So what are you doing here in Chicago following me?
我想知道你知不知道
I was wondering if you had any idea
迈克和林肯在哪儿
Where michaeland lincoln were?
你去哪儿
Where are you going?
你想知道迈克和林肯的事
You want to know about michaeland lincoln?
我在帮助你
I'm trying to help you, man.
还有他们
And them.
你没看新闻吗
Okay don't you watch the news?
他们惹上大麻烦了
They are in a lot of trouble.
非常时期
Big time.
他们唯一的希望就在于
And the only way they can get out of it
你能不能帮我找到他们
Is if you help me find them.
我们只是为了找出
We're just trying to find
刺杀案幕后的两个人
The two men behind the assassination.
很明显你的权限不足以
Obviously your clearance level isn't high enough for you
让你理解我参与的行动
To fully grasp the operation that I have been involved.
好  我们就把已经掌握的情况告诉你
All right then I'll tell you what we have grasped so far.
你搭档的尸体
The dead body of your partner,
尸检表明射杀的的子弹
Autopsy shows the bullet she was shot with
来自官方的武器
Came from agency issued fire arm.
我们找到一些快件
We also got a number of DHL transportation offices with
涉及一个仓库的有趣信息
interesting information concerning a warehouse.
你在洛杉矶执行秘密的行动
back in L.A. that you were conducting a secret operation.
当一个国际政治人物在美国境内
when an international political figure
在美国境内
Is assassinated on american soil
被一个国土安全局的探员
By two men taken into custody
监管下的两个人刺杀
by homeland security agent
所有的证据都显示这个探员已在擅自行动
who by all appearaces has gone rogue
你告诉我们应该怎么想
You tell us what we're supposed to think is going on.
你们现在正在
What's going on is you're
栽赃我是一项和我完全没有瓜葛
Talking to a federal agent like
犯罪行为的同谋
I'm an accomplice to a crime
你是在和一个联邦探员讲话!
That i had nothing to do with.
你知道我效忠国家
You have any idea how many years
多少年了吗
I've served my country?
你知道我为国服务的程度...
Do you have any idea to the extent that I've served...
现在又怎么了  要拷问我?
What is this, Gitmo, now?
我确信
As a homeland agent,
作为国土安全局探员  你一定知道
you are aware, I'm sure
任何妨碍恐怖行动调查的个人
Anyone who impedes an investigation into an
实质上都不享有法律保护
Act of terrorism has virtually no protection under the law.
好吧
Okay, okay.
说
Now.
迈克·斯科菲尔德和林肯·布伦斯到底在哪儿
Where are michael尔·scofield and lincolnon burrows?
我不知道他们在哪儿
I don't know where they are.
好吗
Okay?
但是我能把他们找到
But I can find out.
迈克很显然更关心如何取胜
michael clearly cares more about winning than he
而不是救你的命
does about saving your life.
看来你活不到
Looks like you're not going to
做叔叔的那一天了
Live long enough to be an uncle.
什么
What?
看来莎拉还没有告诉任何人
Well, sara hasn't told anybody.
克里斯蒂娜  巴纳吉找你
christina, banerjee's on the phone.
他想知道他为什么还没有拿到货
He wants to know why he hasn't received the technology.
如果迈克10分钟内还不打电话过来
If michaeldoesn't call in the next 10 minutes
你还不如希望他从来没去福克斯河救你
You're going to wish he'd let you fry back at fox river.
你好
Hello.
我以为我们达成共识了
I thought we had an understanding.
我以为我已经把利害关系都阐述清楚了
I thought I made the stakes crystal clear.
-没错  我在做  -我在克制自己不要杀了莎拉
- You did, and I'm trying. - And I'm trying not to kill sara.
你把东西送过来
That would be a lot easier
就容易多了
If I had something in this hand besides a gun.
这个城市每一个警察都在追查我的下落
Every cop in this city is looking for me.
我最不愿看见的事情
The last thing I want to do
就是被警察抓捕而置她于危险之中
Is jeopardize her life by getting arrested
你想要的一切  被关起来作为证据
What you want locked up as evidence.
而你想要的东西被警方收为证据保存
Have the very thing  you want locked up as evidence.
我很感激你为我的利益着想  迈克
I appreciate you taking care of my interests, michael.
真的
I do.
相信我  就冲你说的
And believe me, for that reason
我会满足你的需要的
I will take care of your interests.
如果一小时内我没看到锡拉
If I don't see Scylla in one
我就让Bagwell尽情玩弄可爱的医生
Hour, I'm unleashing Bagwell to play doctor with the doctor.
听清楚没
Am I clear?
时间太紧了
I need more time.
就一小时
One hour.
迈克就不明白吗
Doesn't michaelunderstand?
他是在玩弄别人的性命
He's playing chicken with other people's lives here.
我的命已经被威胁过一次了
My life's been threatened before.
我不是说你的
I'm not talking about yours.
那个伙计毁了所有我能获得自由的机会
That boy has messed up every chance I've had at freedom.
这是我最后一搏了
This is my last shot.
你真的以为事情结束你就能自由吗
You really think when this is over you'll be free?
比自由更好  我会有工作
Much better than free, I'll be employed.
将军会给我
The General is getting me
一个体面的办公室工作
an honest to goodness job with an office and a desk.
他准备给你什么工作
What kind of job does he gonna get you?
他凭什么相信你
What is he going to trust you  with?
将军雇的是职业杀手  不是业余的
The General hiring professional  killers not amateurs,
更不是没文化的强奸犯
not uneducated criminals who raped them...
管好你的嘴  小美人
You mind your tongue, little lady
事情结束后  你唯一能得到的
The only thing you are getting when this is over is a
是破裂喉咙  和一座无名坟头
slit throat and an unmarked grave.
其实你活下去的唯一可能就是逃出这里
Actually you're only chance at a  life is to get out of here.
而且如果你带我一起走
And if you take me with you.
不管你和迈克之间有何过节
Whatever happened between you
只要你把我交给他
And michael if you get me back to him,
你们就两清了
the slate could be wiped  clean.
迈克和我是绝对不可能两清的
With michael and me, that slate's never going to be clean.
如果他不把东西给将军
And if he doesn't give the General what he wants,
这里会变得无比肮脏的
It's going to get a hell of a lot dirtier.
你在干吗
What are you doing?
我要确认林肯还活着
I need to make sure lincoln's okay.
我想那个小炸弹是要炸我的
I suppose that little explosion was meant for me.
就当做是炸警察的吧
Let's pretend it was for the cops.
拜托  迈克
Please, michael.
闭嘴  你真让自己丢脸
Stop, you're embarrassing yourself.
你现在应该知道姜还是老的辣吧
You should know by now that you can't outthink me.
我总会比你多考虑一步
I'll always be one stepped ahead of you
因为我是你妈
because I'm your mother.
林肯还好吗
Is lincoln okay?
我记得我第一次抓住你撒谎时
I remember the first time I caught you in a lie.
我就能从你眼睛里看出来
I could see it in your eyes just
就像今天这样
Like I could see it today.
让他听电话
Put him on the phone.
你可没资格提要求  儿子
You're not in a position to be making demands, son.
事实上  如果林肯死了
Actually if lincoln is dead, i
我没理由给你锡拉
Have no reason to give you
所以我有这个资格
Scylla which puts me in the position you describe.
知道你还活着真好
It's nice to know you're still breathing.
我还有多少时间
How much time do I have?
不多
Not much.
将军挟持了莎拉
The General has sara.
他给我一小时  用锡拉换她
He's giving me an hour to exchange her for Scylla.
我要知道你们在哪
I need to know where you are.
你能随便给我个有用的信息吗
So if you can give me any kind of signal?
我不知道
I don't know.
如果我要救你们俩
Look, if I'm going to save you both
-我需要信息  任何信息  -又是巴纳吉
- I need something. Anything  -banerjee again.
没多少时间了 迈克
There's not enough time, michael.
我能做到的  林肯
I can do this, lincoln.
我能行的
I can do this.
有件事你得知道
There's something you need to know.
莎拉 怀孕了
sara's...sara's pregnant.
你要做爸爸了
You're going to be a dad.
去救她吧  迈克
Go to her, michael.
我会有办法的  林肯
I'll find a way, lincoln.
时间不够了
There's not enough time.
时间不够了  你
There's not enough time. You...
让我死吧  让我为你做点什么
Let me go out knowing that I did something for you.
给我电话
Give me that.
林肯
lincoln?
不管林肯会怎样  我感到很遗憾
I'm sorry about what's ever happening to lincoln.
我知道你必须保护家庭
And I know you have to protect your family.
我理解
I understand that.
迈克 那我们这些剩下的人呢
But, michael, what are we going to do about the rest of us?
我老婆怎么办
What are we gonna to do about my wife?
阿历克斯
Alex,
我  我不知道你希望我说什么
I don't...I don't know what you want me to say.
你从来不会没有计划
You haven't gone a day in your life without a plan.
别从现在开始
Please don't start now.
我只知道我还有43分钟把这个给将军
All I know is I have 43 minutes to get this to the General.
我不再做计划了
I am done making plans.
其他人都去死吧
And to hell with everybody else.
也许我该学学你了  阿历克斯
Well, maybe it's time I take a page from your book, Alex.
在外场晃悠
Hang out on the sidelines,
观察场地
Survey the field.
当时机来临  再搭上胜利之马
When the time is right, back the winning horse.
我在你眼里是这样的吗
That's what you think I'm about?
跟我说说  阿历克斯
Tell me something, Alex.
你现在在哪匹马上
Which horse are you backing now?
对这问题  我不是很清楚
Because I'm not quite clear on that.
至少你还有得选
At least you got a decision.
他们杀了我儿子
They took my son.
我没得选
I didn't get to choose.
我只是尽全力不失去一切
I'm just trying to do whatever it takes to not lose everything.
我也是
So am I.
如果你能保护帕姆
So if there's something you need to do to protect Pam,
就尽全力吧
you should do it.
你知道在你耍了小花招之后
Do you realize after what you pulled,
对我已经毫无价值了
You're completely worthless to me now?
你这一辈子都毫无用处
You've been worthless to me all your life.
我知道你和迈克认为我是个可怕的母亲
I know you and michaelthink I was a terrible mother.
我完全赞成
I couldn't agree with you more.
我警告过奥尔多
I warned Aldo.
我告诉过他我不是这块料
I told him I was not cut out for it.
不是我的天性
It is not in my nature.
他以前叫我  他的麦克白女士
He used to call me his lady Macbeth.
我就知道我讨厌莎士比亚是有原因的
I knew there was a reason I hated shakespeare.
你讨厌是因为你不能理解
You hated it because you couldn't understand it.
你不能理解是因为
And you couldn't understand it
你的亲生母亲和隔夜的甜甜圈一样蠢
Because your real mother was as dumb as a day-old doughnut.
你问我
You asked me
我怎么就坐看着我儿子去上电椅
how I could just sit and watch my son go into the chair.
答案很简单
The answer's simple really.
你不是我儿子
You're not my son.
迈克已经知道了
michaelalready knows.
肯定是因为这个  他才轻易放弃了你
That must be why it's so easy for him to p  lay with your life.
我想我们是有共同点的
I guess we have that in common.
现在去找我儿子
Now, go find my son.
你的资料会让你被捕
Your information leads to an
我们会保证法庭不会对你动手
Arrest, we'll make sure the courts can't touch you.
你能立字为据吗  然后再做事
Can you put that in writing? And then we'll do business.
不不  你唯一能要求写下的
No, no. The only thing you get to demand in writing
是你的墓志铭
is what we will put on your tomb stone.
你们最不想发生的
The last thing you are gonna want to
就是发现那兄弟俩在外杀人
Find out about is the brothers is killing somebody else,
而你们却在这刁难唯一的线人
While you are in here harassing your only source of intel
那个必须写下来  并由司法部长签字
It's need to be in writing, and signed by the attorney General.
我不相信任何自称为政府工作的人
I don't trust anyone who says they work for the government.
你要做的就是给兄弟俩打电话
All you have to do is call the brothers.
让他们听电话  我来讲
Get them on the phone and let me talk to them.
让他们自己决定  好吗
Then they can make up their own minds, all right?
我不想再搅和这事了
I'm just trying to stay out of all this.
我好不容易家庭团聚
I finally got my family back
不想再次冒险失去他们
And not about so risk losing them again.
我知道现在很幸福
I know this feels good today
那几个月后呢
But what about a couple months from now
你能找的工作都是黑工
When the only job you can get is under the table or
或者贩人蛇  每时每刻
Some labour gill or every minute you will be worrying if
总是担心旁边的人会大声报警
The guy next to you is going to drop the dime in a hard beep
因为他认出你了
because he recognizes you.
找到林肯和迈克又能怎样呢
How is finding lincoln and michaelare changing any of that?
这个人帮我搞定了啊
This guy sought me out, okay?
他了解整件事
He knows everything about the whole thing.
他是谁  是政府的人吗
Who is he? Is he government?
如果他是政府的人  我可不想
'Cause if he's government, I don't wanna...
我开始也不相信他
I didn't trust him first either, okay?
但纸上的东西让我改变想法
But something about being in the pen.
你可以辨认谁是玩家  谁是阿飞
You start to decipher who is a player and who is a punk.
这个人和斯科菲尔德一样  是玩家
And this guy is a player, just like scofield.
现在要做的就是
So the only thing we have to do
告诉他兄弟俩在哪
is tell him where the brothers are,
把那装置还回去  该给谁给谁
Get this device thing back in and so he can put it into the right hands.
然后呢
Then what?
这哥们很牛的
This brother has juice.
他可以抹掉我们所有的记录
He can erase our entire record.
我不是说钱或者浮华的东西
I'm not talking about cash and all that flashy stuff.
是说直接就自由了
I'm talking about straight up freedom.
像正常人一样  听懂没
Living like a man, you feel me?
当然不  南多
No, of course, Nandu.
是是
Yes, yes.
只是出现了一点技术问题
We just ran into a few technical difficulties.
我理解
I understand.
如果你多给我们一点点时间  我就
If you give us a little more Time, then I --
不不  别
no, no, don't.
拜托了  不要登机
Please don't get on the plane.
不  我可以
No, I can...
不
No.
你刚让我损失了7.5亿美元啊
You just cost me 3/4 of a billion dollars.
很好
Good.
至少今天不是完全浪费了
At least the day wasn't a total waste.
我本打算等找到迈克
I was going to wait until I found michael
在他面前杀了你
And just kill you in front of him.
但我准备让你一个人
But instead I'm going to take you out
怎么来的怎么走
the same way you came in, alone.
你最好已经拿到锡拉了
you better be calling me to tell me you've got scylla.
你现在派谁来都太晚了
Whoever you've sent after it is too late.
迈克正要把锡拉去和将军换莎拉
michael's giving scylla back to the general in exchange for sara's life.
你他妈是谁?
Who the hell is this?
阿历克斯·马宏 我们还没见过面
alex mahone. I don't believe we've had the pleasure of meeting.
哦 阿历克斯·马宏
Oh,yeah. alex mahone.
你也想惹我?
You calling to rub this in my face?
我找你是想做一笔交易
Calling to see if  you'll make me an offer.
我能帮你弄到锡拉 你帮我做一些事情
I can get scylla for you,if you promise to give me what michaelcan'T.
比如说?
What's that?
我全家的安全
Protection for my family.
你的人要是能使我妻子摆脱将军的监视
If your people can get my wife away from whoever the general's got watching her,
我就给你锡拉
I'll get you scylla.
- 你能给我弄到锡拉  -马宏...
-You can get me scylla? - mahone...
你这混蛋
you son of a bitch.
Burrows的死活我可不管
I've got no particular love for burrows.
我也不管
Sounds like the feeling's mutual.
对 但这家伙一直对我直言不讳 不像他弟弟
Yeah,but unlike his brother,the guy's always been straight with me.
他还帮我抓住了谋杀我儿子的人
And he helped me track down the guy who murdered my son,and for that,
我欠他的
I owe him.
你就不欠迈克什么
And you don't owe michael?
已经清了  他自找的
Not anymore. His choice,not mine.
好吧
Tell you what.
你给我锡拉
You give me scylla,
要是林肯还能喘气 那就是你的了
if lincolnoln's still breathing,you can have him.
我喜欢这交易
I like that deal.
时间滴答滴
Hickory dickory dock.
斯科菲尔德能来得及么
Tell me,has scofieldever run up your clock?
他够不够男人呢
Has he been man enough to go there?
他要留到新婚之夜么
Or is he saving it up for the wedding day?
迈克比你想象的还男人
michaelis more man than you can ever hope to be.
你怎么知道男人是怎样的
How would you know what a man is like,huh?
跟你比 我干过的男人多得多
Of the two of us,I bet I've been with more of them.
看看你  这么拘谨
Look at you,all buttoned up...
性冷淡
frigid.
告诉我 什么能让你兴奋起来?
Tell me,what does it take to loosen up a gal like you,huh?
音乐?
Music?
鲜花?
Flowers?
还是爱抚?
Touch?
指尖游走到只有迈克...
Where the fingers do the walking down to where only michael...
别说了!
stop it!
拜托
Please.
哦 我就是喜欢有礼貌的女人
My,my. I do like a woman with manners.
迈克告诉我你快到了
michael,you better be calling me to tell me you're close.
- 马上到  - 很好
-We're almost there.  -Good.
但我改主意了
But I've changed my mind.
交易地点由我选
The exchange will be made at a location of my choosing.
原谅我  但我不相信你
Forgive me but I don't really
除非是不熟悉的地方
Trust you, except on unfamiliar territory.
你把莎拉毫发无损地带来
You bring sara unharmed and
见面地方随你挑
I'll meet you anywhere.
这有个停车场
There's an parking lot where
鹈鹕大街和海滩交汇处
Pelican drive meets the beach.
20分钟内到达
Be there in 20 minutes.
我能相信你会让我们好好生活的吧
And I'm supposed to trust you'll let us live our lives?
不管你信不信  迈克
Believe it or not, michael,
世界上我最不想做的事
The last thing I want on earth
就是再次见到你或者你的家人
Is to see you or any member of your family again.
以后井水不犯河水
Just stay out of my way, I'll stay out of yours.
带锡拉给我  20分钟  迈克
Bring me Scylla.20 minutes, michael.
好的
All right.
20分钟啊
20 minutes.
之前我真的以为你是为一己之私
About earlier -- I do think you're in it for yourself.
我很幸运  那意味着你也在我的马背上
Fortunately for me, that's meant you've also had my back.
还不只一次
More than once.
这些事  让我很感激
And for that, I'm grateful.
拿上箱子
Take the case.
走吧
Get out of here.
那帕姆呢
What about Pam?
我会处理好
I got it handled.
祝你好运
Good luck.
看起来你的男朋友
Looks like your boyfriend
捅了篓子啊
Straightened his priorities out.
太糟了
Too bad.
我们才刚开始 熟悉对方
We're just starting to get Familiar.
泰迪  你干什么
Teddy, what are you doing?
你说过我们要
You said we was going to
带她过去交换
Bring her on the exchange.
我今天只想让斯科菲尔德
All I'm giving scofieldtoday
慢慢的死掉
Is a slow death.
那我们怎么
So what are we going to do
处置她
With her?
随你的便
Whatever you like.
似乎我们终于找到了
Perhaps we've finally found a
一个你完全能够胜任的工作了
Job for which you're perfectly Suited.
马宏先生
Mr. mahone?
我在路上了
I'm on my way.
迈克呢
And michael?
我不想谈迈克
I don't want to talk about michael.
貌似迈克没选好  他的朋友啊
It seems michaeldid a poor Job choosing friends.
我们都没得选
None of us choose this.
我们只能选择如何 结束这一切
The only thing we choose is how It ends.
赶紧让你的人准备好
Just get your people in place to
去救我的妻子  怎么样
Help my wife. How's that sound?
我们在局里的线人说
One of our assets with the
两名探员正在迈阿密
Bureau says that two agents are
审问唐·赛尔夫
Questioning Don self at Miami
梅森医院
Mission hospital.
辩护律师刚刚 宣布了他的豁免权
The attorney-general issued a Proclamation for his immunity.
你认为他有威胁吗
You think he's a threat?
可能吧
Perhaps.
问题是对谁
The question is to whom.
喂
Hello?
迈克 我是唐·赛尔夫
michael, it's Don self.
怎么样了
How is it going?
还好  还好
Well, well, well.
我还以为你死了呢
Thought you were dead.
要是我每次对你这么说
If I had a dollar every time
都能得到1美元就好了
I've said that about you.
你听起来怪怪的  唐
You sound funny, Don.
你想怎样
What do you want?
你看见那个混蛋怎么对我妻子的了  是吧
You saw what had that bastard Did to my wife, right?
我要报复
I want revenge.
你在哪  我们可以请求增援
Where are you? So we can call back up.
没这必要
That's not necessary.
这一切就快结束了
This is about to be over anyway.
怎么了
What's going on?
我要挂电话了  唐
I'm hanging up now, Don.
喂
Hello?
斯科菲尔德用的是黑卡［国外居然也有］
scofield's on a burner.
很难追踪
They're harder to trace.
我们还要更多时间
We are gonna need more time.
他会打回来的  他就是有点生气了
He's gonna call back. He gets riled up.
他会打回来的
He'll call back.
杀了人之后打回来吗
After he kills somebody?
你听见了
You heard.
事情很快就会了结
This is about to be over.
让他回来接电话 赛尔夫探员
Get him back on the phone, Agent self.
快点
Now!
那个家伙说
So this cat says that
斯科菲尔德和林肯看见他了
scofieldand lincoln should
会认出来的
Recognize him.
认出来是从哪来的
Recognize him from where?
我不知道
I don't know.
听着  我们经历了很多
Look we've been in a lot of
乱七八糟的事
Messed up places.
我只是想说  这很重要
I'm just saying. It makes differences.
还有  他有没有说
Besides, did he say what he was going
他想怎么处置锡拉
To do with Scylla?
这些人说他们肯定不会让政府来管
All these guys said is that they can't go through the government.
因为没有任何政府
'cause no one government should have
应该有这么大的权力
That much power.
你应该去问问 他本人 他就在那
Look, you want to ask him Yourself. He's right there.
他给你名字了吗
Even give you a name?
他说可以叫他保罗
Said call him Paul.
先生
Sir.
要是有人想跑
If anyone tries to escape,
立刻击毙
Aerate them.
留意任何
Keep an eye out for anything
可以动的东西
Suspicious.
斯科菲尔德狡猾的像下水道的老鼠
scofield's a tunnel rat.
我可不是福克斯河里面唯一一个
You know, I wasn't the only fox in the
晚上睡觉的时候
River fall asleep at night
梦到你那白色大褂下面迷人的胴体的人
Dreaming about treasures was Tucked beneath that white coat Of yours.
每个人都会想入非非
Every guy let their minds Wander.
矿上的任何人都想跟你或者凯蒂玩一玩
Any man at the mines want to $%^ between you and nurse Katie.
有的时候还是你们 两个一起
Sometimes settling on the both Of you.
喜欢吧
You digging that?
这帮老滑头就喜欢
All you old junkies like a
说点荤的
Little dirty talk.
让我看看那些踪迹在哪
Let me see where the tracks are.
我可以的  可以的哦
I think I can, I think I can.
放我走  我可以告诉
Let me go, I can tell the
法庭是你救了我
Courts that you saved my life.
要是你放我走  我可以请求
If you let me go, I can petition
宽大处理
For leniency.
我可以告诉他们是你救了我
I can tell them you saved my life.
我还有我父亲的那些关系
I still have connections from my father.
我总以为
I was always thinking the way
我要报复斯科菲尔德的方式是杀了他
I was going to get revenge on scofieldwas to kill him.
一刀子直插进他的心脏
Driving that knife right into His bleeding heart.
现在站在这  看着你
And now, standing here looking
我想到了比让他去死更狠的了
At you, I'm thinking there's Something worse than death for Him.
求你了  别这样
Please, no.
我会把你完整的送回去
I'll return you in one piece.
但是完整的
But that piece going to be a
也是被糟蹋过的  就这样
Little used. That's all.
每次他再看到你
And every time he looks at you,
每次他跟你在一起的时候  他就会看到  我
Every time he wants to be with You, he's going to see me.
什么都没有
Nothing.
我们得赶回房子去了 快
We got to get back to the loft Now.
迈克
Hey, michael.
又是唐打过来的
This is Don calling back again.
我知道你跟我有过节  好吧
I know you have a beef with me. Alright.
我能理解
And I understand.
我想我能够让我们大家都尽快脱身
I think i have a way to get us All out of this.
你能给我回拨过来吗
Can you please just call me Back?
我们换成B计划之前
How many messages we going to
还要给这家伙留多少信息
Leave this guy before we move on To Plan B?
他会打回来的
He's going to call back.
先生  打扰您一下
Excuse me, gentlemen.
我要查个病人  几分钟就好
I need to check on a patient.Just take a few minutes.
他会打回来的 好吧
He's going to call back, Okay?
大厅那边有咖啡卖
There's coffee down the hall.
他会打回来的  耐心一点  好吗
He's going to call back, just be patient, okay.
会联系上他的
We're going to get him.
怎么样了  医生
How's is going, doc?
很好
It's going well.
你是第一次见我吧
Is this your first time with me?
那是什么
What is that?
我见过你  是吧
I know you, right?
你过去犯毒瘾的时候
Oh, i bet you was a tomcat
肯定是坏透了吧
Back when you was using, huh?
现在呢喜欢看着
Nowadays you like to look a
别人的眼睛
Fellow in the eyes.
但是以前  以前
But back then -- back then, oh,
那时候  我肯定
Back then, i bet the last thing
你最不想做的就是
You wanted to do was see who you
知道自己和谁在一起
Was keeping company with.
你太自私了
That's self worth for you.
我一直觉得
See, I've always felt that the
你选择陪你的人
Partner you choose to be with is
正好反映出
Just a reflection how you're
那个时候你对自己的看法
Feeling about yourself in that Moment.
我得告诉你  美女
And I got to tell you, sister,
现在老泰迪感觉自己
Right now old Teddy is feeling
就像一群雄鹿
Like a million bucks.
没错
Oh, yeah.
我在这件事上要大度一些
And I'm going to be a gentleman About this.
我让你来选
I'm going to let you choose.
你告诉我喜欢怎样的 莎拉
You tell me how you like it, sara.
而我自然会
And I'm going to give you just
谨遵医嘱的
What the doctor ordered.
什么  有话说吗
What, you got something to say?
就在你和你那帮狱友
Just that while you and the
和你那帮狱友晚上
Other cons were taking care of
"自己动手"的时候  凯蒂和我
Yourselves at night, Katie and I were
查了你的医疗记录
Going over your medical records
想找到怎么才能
Trying how best to manage your
搞定你  什么能使你爽
Care, figure out what makes you Tick.
而我记得 西奥多
The thing I remember about you, Theodore?
什么都不能
Nothing makes you tick.
你根本不行
You can't -- tick.
你到底想 说什么
What exactly are you Implying?
你之所以强奸
That the reason you rape and
杀人  制造痛苦  是因为 你不能做爱
Kill and make pain is because You can't make love.
你有神经性勃起障碍
You're got neurogenic e.d.
很可能是由于
Probably caused by injuries you
你小时候受到性虐待时 留下的伤
sustained during your own Childhood sexual abuse.
你撒谎
That is a lie.
撒谎
你随便说 要怎么处置我吧
Talk all you want about what You're going to do to me,
你我都知道 你能做的微乎其微
Theodore. You and i both know there is Very little you can do.
够了
All right.
赶快收回
Now you're going to take back
你说的每一个字
Every word you just said.
听见了吗
You hear me?
没理由感到 惭愧的  泰迪
There's no reason to be Ashamed of it, Teddy.
很多男人都有这样的问题
So many men suffer from it
闭嘴
Shut up!
我不知道哪个更
I don't know what is more
让我难受  是你认为我
Insultingt, you thinking I'm
不举  还是你觉得你能
Challenging or you thinking
从这里逃出去
You're going to break out of Here.
我想想看
Let me think about that.
我猜还是前者
I'm going with the first one.
现在我就让你看看我到底行不行
Now i'm going to show you just How functional I am.
迈克
michael.
求你了
Please.
没事了
It's all right.
过来
Come here.
你没事吧
You all right?
带我离开这儿
Get me out of here.
让我看看
Show me.
进来吧  阿历克斯
Why don't you come inside, Alex
我们还有很多事要谈
We have a lot to talk about.
做交易之前
Before we do any business,
我要你证明帕姆 已经安全了
I'd like some proof that Pam is Safe.
我们的人已经潜入了公司的执行室
We have an asset embedded in The company operations room who
他能获取关于你妻子的地点和方位
Was able to access the details Of the location and the position
的任何信息
Of her bird-dog.
很好
That's great.
但是还不够我要确定她彻底安全
That's not good enough. I need to know that she's in the Clear.
我已经执行了 这个命令
I'm ready to execute that Order.
但是首先我需要你 把锡拉交出来
But first I need you to hand Over Scylla.
将军迟早会意识到我背叛了他
only a matter of time Before the general realizes that I turned my back on him.
还有迈克
And michael.
他发现之后  肯定会报复的
And when he does, he's going to Want revenge.
去打电话
Go make the call.
阿历克斯
Alex.
这一切不是威胁
This isn't about threats.
不是耍手段
This isn't about games.
而是我们就是这样做交易的
This is about how people do Business.
我没得到某种保证之前
I would be a fool if I gave you
是不会傻到
Everything you want before i had
把一切都拱手交给你的
Some kind of guarantee that i'm Going to get everything i want.
你很忙吧
You've been busy.
在这呢
Here it is.
其余的部分呢
Where is the rest of it?
好吧 我已经遵守了约定了
All right. I've kept my end of the deal.
你也该兑现你的诺言了
Time for you to make good on Yours.
请打电话
Make the call, please.
我和林肯马上就走
And lincoln and I will be on our Way.
允许的话  我想在你们出去之前
If it's okay with you, I'd Like to check this out first to
先检查一下
Make sure everything works
以确定一切都能正常工作
Before anybody goes anywhere.
把他关起来
Lock him up.
你来这里干什么
What are you doing here?
救你丫的
Saving your ass.
我不能那么做  莎拉
I couldn't make that choice, sara.
我必须要救你们俩
I had to save you both.
如果你想做些事
If there's something you need
来保护帕姆  你就应该这么做  阿历克斯
To do to protect Pam, you should Do it. Alex.
我们很可能救下所有人
There may be some way we can Save everyone.
坏消息是  我母亲知道
The bad news is my mother can
我会怎么做
Read my every move.
她说这是因为好了解我
She says it's because she knows Me.
好消息是   她不了解你
The good news is she doesn't Know you.
我知道将军
I knew the general would never
肯定不会兑现他的诺言
Honour his end of the Arrangement.
我知道  知道他是不会
I knew -- I knew he'd never
带你去交换锡拉的
Bring you to the exchange.
我只是做了必须做的事
So I did what I had to do.
我们谈论的是 多大规模的爆炸
How big an explosion are we Talking about?
大到足以结束这一切
Big enough to end all this so
这样  我们就能够开始新的生活了
We can -- maybe start something New.
我是说  如果你也愿意的话
I mean, if that's what you're Feeling.
快从桌子上下来
Come on. You got to get off the table,
快
Come on.
我们必须要去房间的另一边
We got to get to the other side Of the room.
快  林肯
Come on, lincoln.
准备好从这个鬼地方出去了吗
You ready to get the hell out of Here?
有问题没收到任何链接
There's something wrong. Not getting any kind of a Connection.
警告  未发现终端设备